Hello I am Hello Sir hey hey
and they don't get tension ok
what is this d current further old
and what about you man chandni
people have other source of income
effect and chandni I actually I do
events and see get compensated event
device sometimes my mother and my bike
also assist me on student dem
through d company and see have bin idea
your company sometimes for same project
gives same amount of money to you your wife
on d project date working on so c
components dem accordingly for date but they do not have
other individual income as such
no I don't have other income ok good and I can you tell me what has happened
with you and the same have
you gathered today what si want tu say today yes I want tu
alert general public let what this happen
and see trusted d ICICI
ok mani
with dem because they take advantage of d
trust and dentry take un mani no every man
2012-14 night taken sorted product bank
you do hd where my manager and I am a common
age trusted dembli this told me date see have some
best schemes give hd and get
and think tax free returns ok
you need to path and diesel liquid investment and if you pay you are
on your get cumulative
interest on debt like de rectang deposit
and Vijay agree and for which I had and pay till like it was an like
₹2 lakh
investment 2012 ok goes dat things started
going word like when did things start going bad
2012-14 so I think I have
seen your details ₹1 lakh
sold in 2012
sent in 2014 un log ne aur
ek policy sold hai ICICI Bank ek policy sold hai Neha Poddar se so I wanted I also wanted you ask about Neha Pota hai but date will come later hi hu
ise no har
Neha
aap ka rhe ki  You bought a policy from ICICI Bank in
2012 and the
offer was sent of long term nature
in which I was not told anything properly
that there is any for future closure in it which actually according to the
guidelines
of IIT they should make the public aware
that if you buy the entire policy and if you do
not pay it then the entire amount will be lost to you,
they themselves
told me this after issuing it and in fact a red
and anti money laundry ex date other
person who is being giving the policy over a
lock should be our source of income should be
verified which is the oldest of the bank
and policy showing the agency which they have
not done anything so they have followed the entire
idea guidelines and anti money
laundering guidelines and the
biggest thing is like I am capable of paying this kind
of interest of like 24 lakhs,
like you are not less,
they did not even ask me for my proof of funds, they did not even
ask how I will pay the money, now I will see now and they have done
their  Manmarzi ek jhoot ke basik ek sakte kar baalik ek sakte kar dete kar sakte hain aapka aapko ...
D employees I will come back to you
Prabha I want to say something
it was an relationship manager
do you know her see don't know having sold you her only so have you ever
met this girl Neha grandson is
you like d person I want
you pass I am Sam Mani in HD so
this is madam in c have go van butor pol
d singing which you can give
you recurring deposit of 15
per cent
cumulative interest you just have to pay
you time
next year it will be like
no recurring type or
cumulative type of d social
bank employees first contacted you
in 2012, 2014, 2017 some policies are being
sold to you Neha, some policies are being sold by Gupta
and some policies are
ok they have a target they
fulfil their target these people sell the policies
in the open market to the agents of their company agents
agents
get commission against the policies so bank
employees do not get commission  What is he doing,
his target is achieved with one
policy, now what are the extra policies that he is buying,
he must be selling them to new Poddar,
I am not sure sir, how would it have happened,
but this is what happens actually on the
ground and he was getting commission,
so it is possible that you are thinking
that I am buying policies from the bank
and this bank employee is
selling the policies in the open market and your
commission is also less, so this is happening
dear, this is the process of pre-ishuans
verification call, by the way, any pre-ishuans
verification call process is with you, they are
absolutely not and no KYC basic is
mandatory, I have believed that for doing any such and issuing such
high amount of
insurance, now basic KYC should be
required and of course,
no Aadhar card etc. must have been taken, there will be
no income tax proof, I have
not sent my email  The address is wrong,
my
bank accounts are somewhere in the bank,
Bin Dan, I have never taken your income
documents.
Sir Yogi Sir, on some forms
you also said that it is not available to you
absolutely because my science you can give it to you
handwriting specialist, there is
no Magi signature from that form and they have
deducted my savings account by itself
on X by giving exclusively
and you have to fill that new policy
shoot by doing
your life
regulation which is hoti I think it was passed
in 2016 all of those rules happen cloud little
I was also looking at the income details that
they have declared on your propose
forms that too is very strange, on
28th of March 2018 a policy was
issued in the name of Yogesh Thakur ji and in that
they have shown you date you are
professional and earning 30 lakhs and in the same
they have issued another policy on 21st March,
no not in the same month before that a
policy was issued in the name of Yogesh sir in
October 2017 and there you got Rs 12 lakhs  You have
shown your income through salary
so I don't know like 30 lakh rupees
something fixed I don't get anything
and event is today not tomorrow unsold income don't
and I have unfixed source of
people have approached the company that I have
bin writing you dem this 9
months and they are lately ignoring and
sending automatic response that they will revert back to you
and this is not their style of
email there is just scripted email that you have bin
you have bought something in 2012-14 in
his complaint is also fine that too
starting from dat branch on this my
sales manager is saying madam
someone has made an ad for you please
go and catch the person who sold you
ICICI bank and ICICI bank is
responsible for this misselling but now take uncharge
ok so what will it do sir c will
highlight your case to d authority and c will
also be highlighting your case on social
media asking people not
bank like  ICICI
with the bank and without giving any
profile information of what you are giving, your
money will be deducted and you will be left with nothing
and you will actually lose all your
life's earnings
communicate the senior management is aware about this
camp but they are not doing anything
and they are turning a blind eye because at the end of the sare se
paisa jo tha yeh
paisa kahan pe park hua and his
profit books it is there it is an
ICICI banks and this has potential because
I have lots of channels ko dekha hai
wo log chahta ke liye thik hai humare
saath hua to hum log share nahi karte hain it is really a very good part of this
insurance selling game no like bank find the
customer for the production
but when you wait the bank also
complaining date this is happen to us through
mens cri ra ra ra samaj karte hain
prudential is a separate
identity but you prudential  Exists See New
Only Bank See New Only from this I am a
65 year old retired person and don't have
income of nothing
of 10 years I don't even know tomorrow I want
you to lie or not this suggest
stupid thing these are basic facts please please please come
down please come down
these are our rules your regulations who
told you this like did you know about this
regulation when did you know about this
aggression traditional policies
how did you come to know about this
deposits till I did not even know
that there is any insurance policy the term
mention or traditional etc I will come to know about this now
well the night you give me some my
fund in fact she started saying that you have to pay for another 10 years
meaning why do you have to pay then
you should forget these words of hers
forget whatever you have paid and it is like
accumulated over the period you are from 2012-17 you should give me some of
8085 luck it is not a small
amount all match of rebellion karne gaya to
mujhe bola ki aur aapko continuo karna padega
while ye saari baatein should have bin toll tu me aate d start when there is an show ye to baat kisa liye something about this major they just told us pay
for 2 years it is like
in India
I completely understand and this is not only
you people who are complaining c have on an
channel insurance angels if you go you have
no more than 300 videos of people
like you who have suffered at the hand of
ICC Bank and ICICI Prudential
and the people are actually what they are doing is date is
completely wrong completely immoral completely
unatical but because c like it is only because
of trusting sambaddi like an
brand like because it is not some
wonder on cooperative thing will no but imagine
like d bank like ICICI would do such a thing
ok  right now when see yes
sir
government you take same stranger action
again because really a lot
of Mani
and infant I would like you to
really because
you are Ajay Gupta and please names
and this video shoot go violin so date
Adarsh ​​are not full d way I want
Linking Road
Dhananjay is d he started all d sing and
c trusted
relationship manager for ICICI bank
manager and including d branch manager
saving account
number
and I definitely highlight and let us see what what
best can be done man date will fight will fight by
highlighting and if I do
n't get any help from there then will stop c will
approach whatever forum c have full definitely
approach
thank you thank you so much
thank you
[music]